{
    "id": "1c6196dfeb424fa9b4e273fbf04db4dc",
    "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………….. somewhat pompous, he was an entertaining companion.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "Although",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………….. a knave nor a fool.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He sells mangoes ………………….. oranges.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "or",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. there is life, there is hope.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "While",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He told me ………………….. he would leave tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. cannot be cured must be endured.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "That",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We love him ………………… he is faithful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "because",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We decided to set out ………………… it was late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "though",
                "although",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The sheep ……………….. the oxen are grazing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "as well as",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………… she looks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "then"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}